UNITE Immigration Project Records 6000/046
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Immigration Project Records
1991-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/046
3.11 cubic feet
3.1 linear ft.
Records.
6960428
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/047: UNITE Muzaffar Chishti Papers
6960428
- UNITE Immigration Cases, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UNITE GEB Immigration Meetings, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UNITE Legal Dept., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UNITE Immigration Notes+ Memos, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- UNITE Surveys, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UNITE Press Releases, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Immigration Project, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 911 Immigration Issues 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- INS Reorganization, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- New York Immigration Coalition, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Build Understanding Creating Change, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Reward Work 2002 Campaign (Box 1, Folder 12)
- UNITE Immigration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- UNITE, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Freedom Ride Gen., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Turnout/VIPs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- IWFR - UNITE!, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Immigration Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 12-2-06 Org. W/S - Lithographers, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 2005 IUC (Box 2, Folder 2)
- May Chen, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- May Chen, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 32BJ Security Campaign, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Immigrant and Labor Rights, 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- SACOM, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- China's Unions, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Chinese
- China 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Vietnam 2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Report on U.S. Labor Delegation to Vietnam, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Work in Freedom, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Garment Industry, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Cornell Labor Programs, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Chinese Unions, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Unseen America, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- UNITE Here!, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Immigration, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- UNITE Here!, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- The New York Immigration Coalition, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- New York Immigration Coalition, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- NYC March for Immigrants Rights, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- UNITE Staff Conference on Representing Immigrant Workers in 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Immigrant Workers, 1991-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Immigrant Legal Services, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Filing a Job Description Charge, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Immigration, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Daily News, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- The 2008 Building Bridges Conference Program (Box 3, Folder 6)
- UNITE! Employees Handbook, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- SSA No Match 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Central Labor Rehabilitation, 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- May Chen, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- NILC, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Balbuena case, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- IRCA Photos as Visual Aids (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Documents, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Working in the USA - Know your Rights! - Creole Version (Box 3, Folder 15)
  cassette tape removed and placed in Media Case, now box 4
- CAPE/IRCA Training Conversation Model (Box 4, Folder 1)